Bart Cusick
213 Artesian Dr.
Garner NC, 27529
bartcusick@hotmail.com

Cell Phone: (919)-673-4578

Web Portfolio: <u>bartcusick.github.io/portfolio\_Page/</u>

## **Full Stack Web Developer**

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

A Full Stack Web Developer with humorous and open-minded personality has always made it easy to communicate and work with others. Eager to learn, extremely adaptable, and quick to pick up new tasks. Always met customer deadlines. Innovative, imaginative, multimedia oriented, and can draw really cool monsters.

TARGET JOB Target Job Title: Full Stack Web Developer

**Alternate Target Job Title:** Web Developer/ Creative Designer **Desired Job Type:** Employee, full time /Contract/Project

Desired Status:Full-Time, Part-TimeDesired Salary:50,000+ USD Per Year

**Site Location:** No Preference

Description of my perfect job:

Creating and designing new, fun, and visually stimulating ways of presenting information through the medium of Web pages, Databases, Api's and Graphics. My Ideal job would require all aspects of web development from graphics to final product implementation. Providing a company with the best E-Learning, illustration, web or graphic design possible.

Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) 15+ years

Date of Availability: Immediately

TARGET COMPANY Category: Internet/E-Commerce

Description of my ideal company:

Im looking for a company that is still excited about being in business. A company that is willing to try new things, rewards good work, and allow us to grow together.

**WORK STATUS** US I am authorized to work in this country for any employer.

**EXPERIENCE** 

9/2017 – present UNC Chapel Hill, NC

Graduate of the UNC Full-Stack Developer Coding Bootcamp

9/2017 – present Etix Morrisville, NC

**Customer support superviser** 

Help customers and vendors with fast friendly accurate information. Supervise other customer support agents and assist with training schedules. Also sell tickets.

3/2002 - Present BartWork! Raleigh, NC

Artist

Custom Artwork, Mural Design and implementation, Painting, Illuistration, Graphic design, Band fliers, T-Shirt Design, Band CD Covers, Comic Book Illustration, Vinyl Signs, Logo Design, Web Design, Company Branding.

7/-06 - 11/13 GCFLearnfree.org Raleigh, NC

Flash Developer II / Web Developer/ Interactivity Designer

Create interactive e-learning courses for adult literacy. Create illustration, 3d design, Game design, and graphic design for www.gcfleanfree.org. Create corporate identity and branding materials.

10/-05 – 4/06 Global Knowledge Cary, NC

**Graphic Designer/ Flash Developer** 

Create Graphics and Interactive Flash files for custom E-Learning courses. Clients Included E-labcorp, GSK, Intel, and Schneider Electric.

6/2003 – 2/06 Skinux Cary, NC

Art Director

Design new and cool animated GUI interfaces for clients such as Kodak, Adobe, x3d,and others. To create artwork for marketing and Corporate branding.

6/2005 – 5/2006 PriceWatch.com San Antonio, TX

**Art Director** 

Design new and cool animated GUI interfaces for Ooodoggy.com and Pricewatch.com. using Flash MX 2004 pro and html. Use action scripting to create a database driven search engine in flash. To create artwork for marketing and Corporate branding. Create characters for video games and video game ideas, and create movie and music reviews.

5/2003 – 5/2005 Anamel inc. Raleigh, NC

Illustrator/ Graphic designer

Create characters and artwork for children books on cd as well as package design.

Create illustrations for children books.

12/2002 - 2/2003 Trifolium Raleigh, NC

Web Developer

Make all of the changes to UGcorps new web site. Create new business cards, Flash animations, and posters.

12/2001 - 2/2002 McKinney&Silver Raleigh, NC

**Web Developer** 

(Contractor) Creating and building online eyeblaster marketing spots, and flash

animations for AUDI.

11/2000 - 6/2001 McKinney & Silver. Inc Raleigh, North Carolina

Web Designer

(Contractor)Responsible for helping update the McKinney & Silver Flash web site, and creating new interface designs.

2/2000 - 10/2000 She She Me. Inc Raleigh, North Carolina

Web Designer/Illustrator/Animator/Graphic Designer

She She Me. Inc

Raleigh, North Carolina

Web Designer/Illustrator/Animator/Graphic Designer(2/00-10/00)

Responsible for designing, creating the shesheme.com web-site and flash web site, animations, characters, and bi-weekly illustrations.

EDUCATION

12/2003 NC State University US-North Carolina-Raleigh

Bachelor's Degree

3 Years Attended

Museum School of Fine Arts US-MA-Boston

**Bachelor's Degree** 

1 year attended.

Massachusetts College of Art US-MA-Boston

**Bachelor's Degree** 

1 semester attended.

Mount Wachusett Community US-MA-Gardner

College

**Bachelor's Degree** 

1 year attended.

**SKILLS** 

Skill Name	Skill Level	Last Used	Experience
HTML 5	Expert	Currently used	15 years
CSS3	Intermediate	Currently used	3 years
Git	Intermediate	Currently used	6 months
Node.js	Intermediate	Currently used	6 months
Javascript	Intermediate	Currently used	6 months
MongoDB	Intermediate	Currently used	6 months
API data	Intermediate	Currently used	3 months
MySQL	Intermediate	Currently used	3 months
React.js	Intermediate	2 years ago	3 months
Flash Cc	Expert	3 year ago	18 years
Photoshop Cc	Expert	Currently used	23 years
Illustrator Cc	Expert	Currently used	23 years
InDesign CS6	Intermediate	10 years ago	5 years
After Effects CS6	Expert	2 years ago	5 years
Dreamweaver	Expert	2 years ago	10 years
StoryLine	Intermediate	7 years ago	1 years
ZBrush	Intermediate	10 year ago	1 years
3D studio Max	Intermediate	10 year ago	1 years
Castemate pro	Expert	15 years ago	5 years
Microsoft Office	Intermediate	Currently used	20 years

**REFERENCES** 

Richard Krueger Skinux

(919)-461-8989 rkrueger@skinux.com Phone Number: Email Address:

Reference Type: Professional

**Dean Sheets** GcfLearnfree.org **Phone Number:** 

(919)-621-5858 Dean@gcflearnfree.org **Email Address:** 

Reference Type: Professional

**Ana Walle** Anamel inc. Owner, Creator

Phone Number: (919)-818-7721 Email Address: anamw@aol.com Reference Type: Professional

Dean Pratt Skinux

(919)-601-4505 **Phone Number: Email Address:** dino@skinux.com Reference Type: Professional

Director of Business

Owner, Creator

Web developer